BLACK FRIDAY SALE 30% Off On All Plans

Offer Ends In:

04

DAYS

05

HRS

28

MINS

04

SECS

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: January 31, 2023

This Privacy Policy (the “**Policy**”) describes how FreeYourMusic app (“**FreeYourMusic**”, “**we**”, and “**our**”) process, collects, uses, protects, and shares your personal data on our website at https://freeyourmusic.com (the “**Site**”), and through the mobile application (collectively, the “**Platform**”). 

FreeYourMusic is a company that protects user privacy, and personal data by taking all relevant measures in accordance with applicable legislation, including the EU Regulation 2016/679 – known as General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

**Data Controller:**

Data of the Personal Data Controller:

Hernas OÜ  
Kentmanni 4  
10116 Tallinn  
Estonia

The Data Controller can be contacted via e-mail: [\[email protected\]](https://freeyourmusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or in writing at the address of the Controller’s office with the note “Data Protection”.

**The purpose of data collection:**

We may collect your personal data when you visit our Platform so that we can improve it. We also collect your personal data when you register or use the Platform so you can use our services in proper manner (“**Services**”). We collect information directly from you, from the third parties, as well as automatically through your use of our Site, Platform and associated services so that enables us to provide and maintain the Platform and, from time to time, develop additional features or functionality. The specific purposes of data collection and use (processing) are the following:

1. to provide, personalize and improve your experience with the Services;
2. to ensure proper flow and management of our database;
3. to understand your listening habits and let you transfer your data between music platforms carefree;
4. to deliver excellent consumer Services and support;
5. to provide proper license keys distribution between Platforms users;
6. to understand how you interact, access and use the Platform;
7. to analyse trends, statistics, and to measure overall Platform effectiveness;
8. to develop and provide technical updates, new features and functionality;
9. to communicate with you about the upcoming projects, advertising, new updates, features & functionality of the Services;
10. to detect, prevent and address the technical and security issues;
11. to monitor feedback on FreeYourMusic’s Services;
12. to pursue legal claims and defence in legal disputes.

We also use the information we collect to analyse, develop and improve the Services. To do this, FreeYourMusic may use third-party analytics providers to gain insights into how our Services are used in order to improve the Services experience.

Sharing your data is voluntary, however, by using our Site and Platform, you agree on Policy and its terms.

Unless otherwise defined in this Policy, terms used in this Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use, accessible at [https://freeyourmusic.com](https://freeyourmusic.com/)

**Information we collect when you use the Platform:**

While using our Platform, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal data that can be used to contact or identify you, among others, your e-mail address, license key order identification number, license key payment confirmation.

FreeYourMusic collects information from electronic devices and music services you connect to with use of our mobile application, including confirmation of the playlist transfer between different music services and tracks used in your playlist.

By adding your favourite songs and creating your music playlist you may develop intellectual property rights to your music playlist. Specific details about the playlist, transfer of the playlist between different music services and intellectual rights, you will find in our Terms of Use, accessible at [https://freeyourmusic.com](https://freeyourmusic.com/).

**Cookie policy**

We use cookies to collect information and learn your internet behaviour pattern and preferences. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of the finest features of our Platform.

Cookies are small data files stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device by a website. You need to know that there are two kinds of cookies:

1. session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and
2. persistent cookies (which stay on your computer or mobile device until you delete it).

**Log files**

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site, which is not linked to any information that allows to identify you. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks or taps. The information is used to track visitor’s movement on the Site, and to gather visitor’s demographic information.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyse such information in order to increase our Platform’s functionality. These third-party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

**Data transfer**

We may share your information with our affiliates, however, we take the protection of your privacy and your personal data very seriously. We always try to ensure that our affiliates comply with the terms of our Policy. If FreeYourMusic becomes involved in a business combination, securities offering, bankruptcy, reorganization, dissolution, or other similar process, we may share or transfer your information in compliance with applicable regulations.

We may share your personal data to:

1. _Third Parties Designated by You_. We may share your personal data with the third parties only when you agree to do so.
2. _Our Third-Party Service Providers and business partners_. We may share your personal data with our third-party Service providers for the purpose of payment processing, customer service, email delivery, analytics, data storage, and other similar services. These third parties are only permitted to use your personal data to the extent necessary to enable them to provide such services to our Platform. They are required to follow our express instructions and to comply with appropriate security measures to protect your personal data.
3. _Corporate Restructuring_. We may share your personal data with our business partners in the event that this is legitimate from a business perspective. For example in the event of transaction negotiation, sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These deals can include any merger, financing, acquisition, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.
4. _Law reasons_. We may disclose your information due to generally applicable rules of law, in particular, due to court orders, legal process, law enforcement requests, legal claims, or government inquiries, and to protect and defend our rights.

This Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information.

**International data transfer**

Your information, including personal data, may be processed and transferred by us and our third-party Service providers to the countries outside the EEA region, in particular the United States where personal data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in the EEA region. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. Your consent to this Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

We would like to ensure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights in accordance with the GDPR laws. Therefore, you have the following rights:

1. _the right to access your personal data_: You can request and you are entitled to obtain any of your personal data we process, where it comes from and what we use it for. You can obtain information about how long we store your data and who receives data about you. Your right to access may, however, be restricted by legislation, protection of other persons’ privacy, and considerations for our business and practices.
2. _the right to rectification and ensure of data_: If you have discovered that the personal information we have about you is incorrect, incomplete or irrelevant, you are entitled to have the data corrected or erased subject to the restrictions that follow from existing legislation and rights to process data.
3. _the right to the restriction of use_: If you believe that the data we have processed is incorrect or incomplete, or if you have objected to the use of the data, you have the right to demand the imposition of restrictions as far as the processing of your personal data is concerned.
4. _the right to data portability_: If you ask us to do so, we will pass on your personal information in a structured, usable format.
5. _the right to object to processing_: You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data if we process it for direct marketing purposes.
6. _the right to make a decision about automated individual profiling_: You also shall have the right to object to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling. In these situations, FreeyYourMusic will guarantee suitable measures to safeguard your rights, mainly the right to human intervention when reviewing such cases. You will be notified if any automated decision-making is performed in relation to your personal data.
7. _the right to withdrawal of consent_: If we process personal data based on your consent, you can withdraw your consent to disclose data at any given time. Please also note that we will continue to use your personal data if we have to fulfil a legal or contractual obligation. 
8. _the right to be forgotten_: The right to obtain from us the erasure of all your personal data given to us under the Policy without undue delay. If you will make such a request, we shall have the obligation to erase all your collected and processed personal data without undue delay.

In case of any concerns of your personal information, feel free to contact us by sending an email at [\[email protected\]](https://freeyourmusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or in writing at the address of the Controller’s office with the note “Data Protection”. We will reply to your request as soon as possible.

**Security**

The security of your personal data is important to us, unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure, nor can we guarantee the security of any transmission or storage system. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with the Site or Platform is no longer secure, please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us, by sending an email at [\[email protected\]](https://freeyourmusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or in writing at the address of the Controller’s office with the note “Data Protection”.

**Data Retention**

We retain information as long as it is necessary to provide the Services to you and others, subject to any legal obligations to further retain such information in a manner consistent with the lawful bases as outlined in the GDPR. Please remember that we retain your given information and data as long as we are legally required or permitted to do so. What is important, we can also retain your personal data as long as it results from generally applicable law. Information may persist in copies made for backup and business continuity purposes for additional time. The information we retain will be handled in accordance with this Policy.

**Children's Information**

No one under 13 is authorized to use our Platform. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has shared with us personal data, please immediately contact us by sending an email at [\[email protected\]](https://freeyourmusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or in writing at the address of the Controller’s office with the note “Data Protection”. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from children under age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers and we will delete such information from our files as soon as reasonably practicable.

**Complaints and disputes**

We are committed to resolving any complaints about your personal data. If you would like to lodge a complaint regarding this Policy or our business practices in relation to your personal data, please contact us by sending an email at [\[email protected\]](https://freeyourmusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or in writing at the address of the Controller’s office with the note “Data Protection”. We will reply to your complaint as soon as we can.

**Changes to this policy**

We will post any modifications or changes to the Policy on this page. We reserve the right to modify the Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review it frequently. 

**Contact information**

We may use your personal data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Policy and/or practices, please contact us by sending an email [\[email protected\]](https://freeyourmusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or in writing at the address of the Controller’s office with the note “Data Protection”.  

**External services**

The Platform and Mobile App uses YouTube API Services to facilitate transfer of playlists to and from YouTube. Please read [Google Privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) before authenticating your YouTube account.

Company

Trust & Legal

Support

* [\[email protected\]](https://freeyourmusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

©2024 FreeYourMusic.com
